▍2026 国家银行公开赛（多伦多）决赛
斯瓦泰克 6-2 6-3 莱巴金娜 · 赛后亚军致辞
Thank you guys.
谢谢大家
It's tough to find words.
一时不知道该说什么
The tank was half empty today.
今天油箱只剩一半
I tried my best but it wasn't enough.
我尽力了但还不够
Uh just congratulate EGA
祝贺伊加
and her team with a great tournament
和她的团队 这一站打得很棒
and uh of course guys, thank you
当然 谢谢大家
so much for incredible atmosphere.
这么棒的氛围
It it was an amazing tournament
这是一届了不起的赛事
and I'm really hope I
我真的希望
can come back very soon here.
能很快再回到这里
I also would like
我还想
to say thank you to everyone
谢谢每一个人
who made this tournament possible.
让这届赛事得以举办的人
Tournament director, all the sponsors,
赛事总监 所有赞助商
Rogers, National Bank,
罗渣士 国家银行
and of course all the volunteers this couple
当然还有这几周
of weeks and uh B kids sharers, everyone.
所有志愿者 球童 每一个人
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
And last uh of course thank you
最后 当然要谢谢
to my team guys.
我的团队
Without you it won't be impossible
没有你们
to get to the final and just hope
我不可能打进决赛 也希望
that we can keep on going.
我们能继续走下去
And of course thank you to the rest
当然也要谢谢
of the team who is not there here
团队里没能到场的人
and uh I see you guys very soon
很快就能见到你们
and hopefully we can carry
希望我们能延续
on the good things
这些好的势头
and uh yeah just uh keep going
继续走下去
and go deep.
走得更远
Thank you.
谢谢